{
  "collection": {
    "name": "German - Czech - Barvy",
    "description": "German - Czech - Barvy",
    "hidden": "false"
  },
  "cards": [
    {
      "front": "blau",
      "back": "modrý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "braun",
      "back": "hnědý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "gelb",
      "back": "žlutý, žloutkově žlutý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "grau",
      "back": "šedý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "grün",
      "back": "zelený",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "lila",
      "back": "fialový",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "orange",
      "back": "oranžový",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "rosa",
      "back": "růžový",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "rot",
      "back": "červený, rudý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "schwarz",
      "back": "černý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    },
    {
      "front": "weiß",
      "back": "bílý",
      "urlOfFrontImg": "",
      "urlOfBackImg": "",
      "collectionId": 1,
      "collectionName": "German - Czech - Barvy",
      "lastShow": null,
      "nextShow": "01-01-1970",
      "interval": 2,
      "hidden": "false",
      "dirty": "false",
      "ef": 2.5,
      "numberOfIteration": 1
    }
  ],
  "settings": {
    "id": 1,
    "playVoiceText": "true",
    "languageOfVoice": "de",
    "typeOfVoice": "f2",
    "volumeOfVoice": 100,
    "displayAnswer": "false",
    "displayAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "limitTAnswer": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTime": 60,
    "showAnswerTime": "false",
    "limitTAnswerByRepeating": "false",
    "maximalAnswerTimeByRepeating": 60,
    "showAnswerTimeByRepeating": "false",
    "filteringCards": "true"
  }
}
